{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"1.75/7",
			"answer":"1.75/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"15.4/0.2",
			"answer":"15.4/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"0.962/0.002",
			"answer":"0.962/0.002",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.64/0.8",
			"answer":"0.64/0.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"71.2/0.008",
			"answer":"71.2/0.008",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1.11/002.03",
			"answer":"1.11/002.03",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.996/0.04",
			"answer":"0.996/0.04",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"68.4/0.2",
			"answer":"68.4/0.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"840/0.6",
			"answer":"840/0.6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.56/0.004",
			"answer":"4.56/0.004",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}

	]
}